ffsng.com 2017-06-07

# FFSNG Privacy Policy

FFSNG Privacy Policy 

the following text is intellectual property of datasteam technologies and copying is strictly prohibited 

Updated at November 21, 2016 

This Privacy Policy applies to ffsng.com owned and operated by Datasteam Technologies SA ("we","FFSNG"). This Privacy Policy describes how Datasteam Technologies SA collects, uses, shares and secures the personal information you provide. It also describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal information.

We are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this website prior to the change becoming effective. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  * Your name, profile picture and date of birth.
  * The email address you used to create a stand alone account or shared through facebook.
  * Your facebook numeric id when facebook is used to connect.
  * Your public IP address which is publicly provided by your Internet Service Provider which may represent your current location.
  * The browser agent string that is sent by your browser to our servers.
  * The type of the device you are using (desktop/mobile).
  * All data generated in the application.

What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

  * Internal record keeping.
  * Notify you about ingame activity.
  * We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  * We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at support@ffsng.com.

How we protect minors

There are 2 age groups in the game, adults and minors. Users in the same group (adults-adults and minors-minors) can fully communicate with each other. Users in different groups (adults-minors or minors-adults) are not able to lock, raise, wishlist eachother, exchange private messages, gifts, nudges, friend requests and their communication is limited to public only so that it can be screened by our content moderators.

In addition, an adult can not delete his/her messages from a minor's wall. We are also actively monitoring the validity of users' birthdate and we remove users who set a false birthdate without any prior warning since protecting minors is our highest priority.

In short, anything that may create an unattended and permanent connection to a minor is disabled. All these measures (including blocking adult/spammy/unsafe sites/images) along with 24/7 moderation and parental guidance which is required when minors are exploring the internet, make the game a safer place for all.

Passive Collection

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

Tracking technologies

FFSNG and its partners use cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users' movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

To manage Flash cookies, please click [here](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager07.html).

Advertising

We partner with a third party to display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) or if you are located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

Email or newsletter

If you would like to discontinue receiving any information through your email, you may update your email preferences by using the "unsubscribe" link found in emails we send to you or at your member profile on our website or by contacting us at support@ffsng.com.

Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Private messages in FFSNG

Private chat is just private. That means no other player, moderator or unauthorized user can see what you two say to each other. But you should avoid sending sensitive personal information such as passwords or credit card numbers. Please also note that your private posts are subject to your home country's applicable laws and we take no responsibility for them. You can also use the application provided report feature to report inappropriate content in order to take appropriate action.

Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Upon request FFSNG will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by logging in to your account. We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.
  * Whenever you feel that you want to remove yourself from the game you can deactivate your account using the ingame account control panel or the default facebook application removal procedure in case you are using your facebook account to access FFSNG.
  * If you wish your data to be completely removed including your name, facebook id, picture, email and any ip traces, please end us an email at support@ffsng.com with your request. Keep in mind that you will not be able to reactivate your account after the data removal has been processed.

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so. We may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which we think you may find interesting if you tell us that you wish this to happen. If you do not want us to share your personal information with these companies, contact us at support@ffsng.com.

We may share your information with third parties who provide services on our behalf to help with our business activities. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.

These services may include:

  * Fulfilling orders.
  * Providing customer service.
  * Payment processing.

In certain situations, FFSNG may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or other legal process, when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request. If FFSNG is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information. We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.

If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution provider (free of charge) click [here](https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request).

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the support@ffsng.com and we will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

Contact information

Datasteam Technologies SA, Iros Konstantopoulou 28 - 16121 Athens/Greece, contact@datasteam.com
